<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HeartBeep</string>

    <string name="no_watches_connected">No watches connected!</string>
    <string name="no_watches_available">No watches available!</string>
    <string name="high_risk">High Risk</string>
    <string name="no_risk">You\'re good to go!</string>
    <string name="medium_risk">Medium Risk</string>
    <string name="low_risk">Low Risk</string>
    <string-array name="low_risk">
        <item>Eat a healthy diet. Try to limit saturated fats, foods high in sodium, and added sugars. Eat plenty of fresh fruit, vegetables, and whole grains. </item>
        <item>Limit the alcohol. Don\'t take more than 2 alcoholic drinks per day.
Make sure that you get enough sleep. If you don\'t get enough sleep, you raise your risk of high blood pressure, obesity, and diabetes. Make sure to get 7 to 9 hours per sleep every night.</item>
        <item>Exercise regularly. Exercising strengthens your heart and improves your circulation. It lowers cholesterol and blood pressure, two factors which directly affect the health of your heart.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="medium_risk">
        <item>Know your numbers! Always keep your blood pressure, cholesterol, and glucose levels in check!</item>
        <item>Pay attention to your symptoms! If you feel extremely tired or fatigue, changes in your heart rhythm, shortness of breath, go see a doctor!</item>
        <item>Reduce stress! Stress is a major factor in heart diseases and strokes. It may induce overeating, overdrinking, oversmoking, and all factors that affect the health of your heart. </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="high_risk">
        <item>See a doctor immediately! </item>
        <item>See a doctor immediately! </item>
        <item>The numbers show that you have a high risk of having heart diseases, therefore you need to keep yourself under check!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="no_risk">
        <item>You\'re good to go! </item>
        <item>Your heart is satisfied with how you are treating yourself! </item>
        <item>Keep exercising, continue your nutritious diet, and stay away from smoking and alcohol!</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
